At the beginning, we are using Copilot
Studio because it's
easy to create your first agent. Each
day, we are creating more complex agents
with Copilot Studio. Especially with the
Business Central MCB server, the
solution
is now in one hotel, but we want to
create a reusable solution. With Copilot
Studio, it's very easy.
>> We strongly believe that Business
Central is the best technology product
out in the market. And we, as a payroll
solution, adopt all that technology on
top of Business Central. We see that
smaller businesses outsource their
payroll because of the complexity. With
Agent and Copilot, we can help smaller
companies to in-house payroll again.
>> The biggest wins with the payroll agent
is that it automates a lot of those
tasks that rely on manual data entry.
Using the toolkit from Microsoft and all
of the Copilot capabilities, along with
the new custom agents that we can build,
forms an epic package no other
competitors in the market really have
outside of the Microsoft platform.
>> Aptn is an AI-first company. We have a
lot of other ERP systems and operational
solutions in our portfolio, but Business
Central is our main driver because we
can build on top of this with our
vertical industry solutions. Often, you
see customers who are playing around
with AI in their private life, but have
not really seen what is the business
value, what's the impact on their own
companies when they would implement AI.
And what we bring is the
industry-specific
agents from Business Central, for
example, our manifest purchase order
creation agent or the sales claim agent.
And this is really what they can see,
ah, this is why we should use AI.
>> Our agents are completely reusable. It's
for every customer, for every partner.
It's not a black box. We are based
normally in Business Central, so we try
to develop the most of them in Business
Central. On top of that, we're using
also Copilot Chat. It's completely
changing how we develop it towards
back-driven development.
>> My biggest recommendation to any
partner,
start as soon as possible. Make a small
step forward.
>> Don't try to solve all the problems. Try
to solve one
problem, one issue.
>> Bringing preconfigured agent with
specific industry needs, that's what
brings us the best opportunities for the
future.